Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Chancellor Records, 1933-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1933-2011, UWM Archival Collection 46; 220.4 cubic ft. (224 boxes) 2 film reels 718 digital files (539 MB)
  - 2. Baum Administration Records, 1972-1983
    - Department of Psychology, 1970-1979 (Box 42, Folder 17-18)
    - Department of Registration and Records, 1977-1979 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Department of Slavic Languages, 1976-1978 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Department of Sociology, 1970-1975 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Department of Spanish and Portuguese, 1971-1973 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Department of Spanish and Portuguese, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Department of Student Activities, 1970-1975 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Department of Urban Affairs, 1973-1976 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Disciplinary Guidelines, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Discrimination Cases, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Division of Facilities and Services, 1973-1977 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Division of Natural Sciences, 1969-1977 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Division of the Professions, Executive Committee, 1970-1978 (Box 43, Folder 8-9)
    - Division of the Social Sciences, 1970-1978 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Division of Urban Outreach, 1973-1980 (Box 43, Folder 11-18)
    - Division of Urban Outreach
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - Off-Campus Credit Courses, 1973-1975 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - Off-Campus Credit Courses, 1976-1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Office of the Dean, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Divisional Space Analysis, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Drop Policy, 1974-1976 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Drug Research, 1974-1979 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Education, General Topics, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Emeritus Status, 1973-1978 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Employee Assistance Program, 1976-1979 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Employee Relations Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Employment Relations Office, 1973-1975 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Energy Conservation, 1979-1981 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Engelmann Field, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - English Proficiency Testing Program, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Enrollment, 1973-1979 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Enrollment Ceilings, 1975-1977 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Enrollment Data, 1977-1979 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Enrollment Project, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 17-18)
    - Enrollment Projections, 1973-1981 (Box 44, Folder 19-20)
    - Enrollment Shortfall, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Enrollment Statistics, 1974-1978 (Box 44, Folder 22-24)
    - Enrollment Targets, 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Enrollment Targets Task Force, 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 2-4)
    - Enrollment Trends, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Enrollment Trends Task Force, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Environmental Instruction Inventory, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Equal Opportunity, 1975-1978 (Box 45, Folder 8-14)
    - Equal Opportunity Office, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Equal Opportunity Officer, Search and Screen Committee, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Executive Pay Plan, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 17-18)
    - Experimental Program in Higher Education, 1972-1977 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Facilities Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1976-1978 (Box 45, Folder 20-22)
    - Facilities Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Faculty and Staff, Layoffs and Terminations, 1972-1975 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Awards, 1971-1978 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Compensation, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Development Plan, 1977-1979 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Divisions, 1973-1975 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Information, 1974-1979 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1973-1980 (Box 46, Folder 9-10)
    - Faculty Preference Survey on Economic Benefits, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Sabbatical Program, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1970-1977 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Senate, 1972-1978 (Box 46, Folder 14-15)
    - Faculty Senate, Housing Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Welfare Committee, 1970-1974 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Fee Schedules and Policies, 1974-1979 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Field Stations, 1973-1979 (Box 46, Folder 19-22)
    - Financing Higher Education, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Fire Academy Proposal, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - FOCUS Camp Manual, undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Freshman Class Surveys, 1971-1978 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Freshman Seminar Program, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Fringe Benefits, 1973-1979 (Box 46, Folder 28-29)
    - Golightly, C.L., Memorial Service, 1976, 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 141)
    - Grade Review Board, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Assistants, Guidelines for Appointment and Employment, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Deans Committee, 1972-1977 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Graduate School, 1973-1979 (Box 47, Folder 4-20)
    - Graduate School, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
    - Graduate School
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Fee Policies, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Graduate and Professional Opportunities Program, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Institutional Review Board for the Protection of Human Subjects, 1974-1978 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Proposal for Master of Computer Science Program, 1978-1980 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Proposal for Master of Urban Planning Program, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Research Committee, 1974-1979 (Box 48, Folder 9-10)
      - Research Proposals, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 11-19)
      - Research Proposals, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Grants and Contracts, 1973-1976 (Box 49, Folder 2-7)
    - Grants and Contracts, Letters of Thanks, 1973-1976 (Box 49, Folder 8-11)
    - Great Lakes Research Facility, 1971-1976 (Box 49, Folder 12-15)
    - Great Lakes Research Facility, Director, Search and Screen Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Greater Milwaukee Survey of Social Welfare and Health Services, 1971-1976 (Box 49, Folder 17-18)
    - Handicapped Self-Evaluation, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Higher Educational Aids Board, 1973-1977 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Homecoming Task Force, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Honorary Degrees Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Honorary Degrees Committee, 1974-1980 (Box 50, Folder 1-4)
    - Honorary Societies, 1971-1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Honors Program, 1973-1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Human Rights Committee, 1971-1978 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Information Programs for Prospective Students, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Institute for Mineral and Solid Fuel Technology, 1973-1978 (Box 50, Folder 9-12)
    - Institute of Politics Proposal, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Institute of World Affairs, 1970-1980 (Box 50, Folder 14-17)
    - Institutional Research, 1970-1974 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Institutional Studies, Fact Book, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Instructional Media Laboratory, 1969-1978 (Box 50, Folder 20-21)
    - Interim Faculty Consultative Council, 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - International Conference on the Unity of the Sciences, 1976-1978 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - International Councils on Higher Education, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - International Studies and Programs, Office of the Dean, 1970-1976 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - International Water Resources Association, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Johnson Foundation, 1969-1979 (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
    - Joint Administrative Committee on Academic Affairs, Vocational and Adult Education, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Junior League of Milwaukee, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Labor Leaders, 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Labor Relations, 1973-1977 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Labor Relations Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Laboratory for Surface Studies, 1973-1978 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Language and Area Center for Latin America, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Lapham Hall Remodeling Subcommittee, 1973-1978 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Law School Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Laws and Regulations, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Layton School of Art, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Lecture Halls Subcommittee, 1976-1978 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Legislative University Advisory Housing Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Library, 1971-1980 (Box 51, Folder 17-25)
    - Library Committee, 1971-1977 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Library, Office of the Director, 1971-1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Life Science and Allied Health Building Subcommittee, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Limited Appointments, 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Living-Learning Center, 1972-1976 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Manpower Projections, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Media Chronicle of UWM Formation (1954-1956), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Medical Center of Southeastern Wisconsin, 1974-1977 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Medical College of Wisconsin, 1973-1977 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Medical College of Wisconsin/UWM Liaison Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Medical Technology Program, 1973-1976 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Merger Guidelines Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 12-13)
    - Merger, Student Rights and Responsibilities, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 14-15)
    - Meteorology Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 52, Folder 16-19)
    - Midwestern Nursing Research Society, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Military Science Department, 1971-1978 (Box 52, Folder 21-24)
    - Milwaukee Area Manpower Planning Council, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Milwaukee Area Technical College, 1971-1975 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Milwaukee County, 1971-1976 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Milwaukee Educational Foundation, 1973-1976 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Milwaukee Humanities Program, 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 5-6)
    - Milwaukee Science and Technology Utilization Council, 1974-1976 (Box 53, Folder 7-8)
    - Milwaukee Symphony Orchestra, 1973-1979 (Box 53, Folder 9-11)
    - Milwaukee Urban Observatory, 1973-1976 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Minority and Disadvantaged Students Enrollment, 1972-1978 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Minority and Disadvantaged Students Planning Task Force, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Minority and Disadvantaged Students, Support Programs, 1974-1980 (Box 53, Folder 15-16)
    - Minority Recruitment, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Mission Statement, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Mission Statement, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Mission Statement, Public Hearing, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Mitchell Hall, 1974-1979 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Multi-Cultural Conference, 1979 (Box 138, Folder 33)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1972-1979 (Box 53, Folder 22-24)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1973-1979 (Box 54, Folder 1-3)
    - National Commission on Accrediting, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - National Science Foundation, 1973-1979 (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
    - Native American Studies Program, 1973-1979 (Box 54, Folder 7-8)
    - Nursing Building Subcommittee, 1969-1974 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Occupational Therapy Program, 1972-1978 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Office of Secretary of the Faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Office of the Assistant Chancellor, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Office of the Chancellor, Miscellaneous, 1969-1979 (Box 54, Folder 13-14)
    - Office of Women's Studies, 1974-1979 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Ombudsman, 1974-1976 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Ombudsman, Search and Screen Committee, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Open House Task Force, 1974-1978 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Parking and Transit Office, 1972-1978 (Box 54, Folder 19-20)
    - Personnel Office, 1970-1980 (Box 54, Folder 21-25)
    - Pharmacy Program Termination, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1968-1977 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Physical Education Building, 1972-1979 (Box 55, Folder 3-5)
    - Physical Plant, 1970-1975 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Polish-American Studies, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Postal Strike Task Force, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Printing and Duplication Services Task Force, 1974-1977 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Probationary Appointments, 1973-1976 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Program Directions, 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Promotions, 1974-1976 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Public Information, 1973-1976 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Public Relations, 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Purchasing Office, 1973-1978 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Racial and Ethnic Minority Students, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Radio and Television Programs, 1973-1979 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Receptions, 1974-1979 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Regents Statewide University Planning Task Force, 1973-1975 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Registration and Records, 1975-1977 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Registration Deposit, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Research Professorships, 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Research Publications by Werner Baum, 1953-1978 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Residence Halls, 1974-1978 (Box 55, Folder 24-28)
    - Sabbatical Leave Program, 1973-1976 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Sabbatical Leave Program, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
    - Salvation Army Volunteer Probation Counselor Program, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Sandburg Education Center Report, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Satellite Campuses, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Save A Kilowatt Corporation, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - School of Allied Health Professions, 1974-1981 (Box 56, Folder 7-15)
    - School of Allied Health Professions
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder 16-17)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - School of Architecture, 1969-1974 (Box 56, Folder 20-21)
    - School of Architecture and Urban Planning, 1975-1980 (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
    - School of Architecture and Urban Planning
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1974 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - School of Business Administration, 1973-1980 (Box 57, Folder 6-14)
    - School of Business Administration
      - Advisory Council, 1970-1979 (Box 57, Folder 15-16)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 57, Folder 17-18)
      - Economics Building Subcommittee, 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Program Proposals, 1974-1977 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - School of Education, 1972-1973 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - School of Education, 1974-1979 (Box 58, Folder 1-8)
    - School of Education
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 58, Folder 9-10)
      - Pre-School Education Project, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - School of Fine Arts, 1971-1980 (Box 58, Folder 12-20)
    - School of Fine Arts
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Film Art Degree Program Proposal, 1974-1976 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Office of the Dean, 1970-1975 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - School of Library and Information Science
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Director, Search and Screen Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - School of Library Science, 1972-1978 (Box 59, Folder 6-7)
    - School of Library Science
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Director, Search and Screen Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - School of Nursing, 1973-1979 (Box 59, Folder 10-21)
    - School of Nursing
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder 22)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - School of Social Welfare, 1973-1979 (Box 60, Folder 2-6)
    - School of Social Welfare
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 60, Folder 7-8)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 9-10)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - Operation Intervention, 1971-1975 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Science and Technology Utilization Council of the City of Milwaukee, 1974-1979 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Search and Screen Committees, 1977-1978 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Secretary of the University, 1974-1977 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Secretary of the University, Search and Screen Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Segregated Fee Advisory Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Segregated Fee Allocation Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Segregated Fees, 1976-1980 (Box 60, Folder 19-20)
    - Society for College and University Planning, 1974-1979 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Southeast Wisconsin Regional Consortium, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Space Management Office, 1971-1976 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Space Management Planning, 1973-1979 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Spanish Speaking Outreach Institute, 1973-1978 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Special Task Force on UWM Grievance Procedures, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Baum, 1973-1980 (Box 61, Folder 2-3)
    - Sponsored Research
      - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 61, Folder 4-7)
      - Reports, 1976-1980 (Box 61, Folder 8-11)
    - State Employee Regular Contribution to Health, 1973-1976 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - State Ethics Board, 1976-1978 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - State Executive Salary Plan, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Stowell Houses, Sale, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Student Advisory Council to the Chancellor, 1973-1980 (Box 61, Folder 16-20)
    - Student Affairs, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Student Association, 1974-1980 (Box 61, Folder 22-29)
    - Student Attraction Task Force, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Student Charges, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Student Conduct Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Student Court, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Student Evaluation of Instruction, 1974-1976 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Student Financial Aids Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Student Government, 1972-1975 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Student Health Services, 1964-1980 (Box 62, Folder 7-8)
    - Student Meetings With the Chancellor, 1974-1976 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Student Pay Plan, 1974-1975 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Student Retention, 1978-1979 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Student Statistics, 1972-1974 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Student Union, 1973-1977 (Box 62, Folder 13-14)
    - Subcommittee on Transportation and Parking, 1973-1975 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Summer Sessions, 1973-1978 (Box 62, Folder 16-18)
    - Task Force on Limited or Program Specific Fiscal Emergency, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Task Force on Student Employment, 1972-1973 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Task Force on UWM Urban Extension Organization, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 21-22)
    - Tenure Data, 1973-1979 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Title IX Task Force, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Transfer Policy, 1972-1977 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Transportation, 1976-1981 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Transportation Office, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Transportation Office, UBUS,1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Travel, 1976-1980 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Travel Policies, 1973-1978 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Tribute, Werner Baum, 1979, VHS video (Box 141)
    - Trust Funds, 1973-1974 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Undergraduate Teaching Improvement Grants, 1973-1981 (Box 63, Folder 4-5)
    - United Council of University of Wisconsin Student Governments, 1976-1980 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - United Nations University, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1973-1979 (Box 63, Folder 8-10)
    - United States, White House Conferences and Programs, 1975-1978 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - University Committee, 1971-1980 (Box 63, Folder 12-17)
    - University Committee, Task Force on Medical Education, 1973-1974 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - University Committees, 1971-1974 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research, 1978-1981 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - University Development, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - University Development, 1975-1980 (Box 64, Folder 1-4)
    - University Development, Director, Search and Screen Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - University Faculty Assembly, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - University Faculty Council, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - University Legal Clinic, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - University Museum Committee, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - University National Bank, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - University of Haifa, 1974-1979 (Box 64, Folder 11-12)
    - University of Missouri, Multicampus University System Study, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - University of Wisconsin Center System, 1971-1978 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - University of Wisconsin Extension, 1972-1981 (Box 64, Folder 15-23)
    - University of Wisconsin Extension Reorganization, 1972-1973 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - University of Wisconsin Legislative Newsletter, 1973-1978 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - University of Wisconsin, Madison Campus, Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - University of Wisconsin Sea Grant College Program, 1974-1977 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - University of Wisconsin System, 1972-1980 (Box 65, Folder 1-3)
    - University of Wisconsin System
      - Administrative Staff Meetings, 1973-1979 (Box 65, Folder 4-5)
      - Affirmative Action Planning, 1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Center for the Study of Minorities and the Disadvantaged, 1978-1979 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Provost for University Outreach, 1974-1976 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Urban Corridor Consortium, 1974-1980 (Box 65, Folder 9-10)
    - University Police, 1973-1979 (Box 65, Folder 11-14)
    - University Police Committee, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - University Police, Director, Search and Screen Committee, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - University Relations, 1975-1978 (Box 65, Folder 17-23)
    - University Relations, 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
    - University Services, 1973-1979 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - University Special Student Category, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - University Special Student Office, 1978-1979 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - University Student Government, 1971-1974 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - University Student Publications Board, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Upward Bound Program, Audit, 1974-1976 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Urban Planning, Degree Program Proposal, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Urban Research Center, 1974-1977 (Box 66, Folder 10-12)
    - Urban Water Resources Research Conference, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Use of University Facilities, 1973-1977 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - User Fees, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Veterans Programs and Services, 1971-1979 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Vice Chancellor, Search and Screen Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 66, Folder 17-20)
    - Vice Chancellors, 1975-1979 (Box 66, Folder 21-23)
    - Wisconsin Academy of Sciences, Arts and Letters, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Wisconsin Alumni Research Foundation, 1972-1977 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Wisconsin Association of Higher Education, 1972-1977 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Wisconsin Coordinating Council of Women in Higher Education, 1972-1973 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Wisconsin Humanities Committee, 1974-1977 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Wisconsin State Employees Union, 1973-1977 (Box 67, Folder 1)